Guide to the United Federation of Teachers Photographs PHOTOS 019
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: New York Teacher Photograph Files, 1951-1987.
  - Subseries I:C: American Federation of Teachers.
    - Sub-subseries I:C:3: Miscellaneous
      - Farmingdale HS, QuEST, Dec 16, 1972 (Item 2293)
      - QuEST Consortium seeks solutions to Public Education Problems, May 1973 (Item 2565)
      - QuEST Reading Workshop, Nov 10, 1973 (Item 2765)
      - AFT Executive Council, 1974 (Item 3275)
      - AFT Presidents Conference, Apr 1974 (Item 2955)
      - AFT Mid-Western Regional Conference, May 1974 (Item 3028)
      - AFT QuEST, Chicago, May 1974 (Item 3029)
      - AFT QuEST Luncheon, Al Shanker, Dave Selden, and Ralph Nader, May 1974 (Item 3110)
      - AFT College Organizing Meeting at UFT Headquarters, Oct 1974 (Item 3390)
      - QuEST Consortium, course in Spanish, Nov 1974 (Item 2565)
      - AFT Higher Education Conference, Nov 1974 (Item 3415)
      - Slaiman, Don at [AFT] State Federation Conference, Dec 1974 (Item 3470)
      - AFT State Federation Conference, Dec 1974 (Item 3470)
      - AFT QuEST, Jun 1975 (Item 3664)
      - QuEST Seminar on Early Childhood, Jan 1976 (Item 4087)
      - AFT National Advisory Commission on Higher Education Executive Committee, Mar 1976 (Item 4185)
      - AFT QuEST, May 1976 (Item 4162)
      - AFT QuEST, May 1976 (Item 4294)
      - Meany, George and Al Shanker, AFT QuEST, May 1976 (Item 4295)
      - AFT State Federation Presidents Meeting, Oct 1976 (Item 4711)
      - Latin American trade unionsts visit AFT, Ed Espillat serves as guide, Nov 1976 (Item 4709)
      - [AFT] State Federation Presidents Conference, Dec 1976 (Item 4755)
      - AFT Crisis Commission on NYC Schools, School Finance Conference, Mar 1977 (Item 3884)
      - Paraprofessionals, AFT Para Conference, 1979 (Item 612)
      - Hill, Velma, AFT Para [Paraprofessional] Conference, 1979 (Item 1079)
      - Van Blake, Barbara, AFT Para Rep. Conference 79, 1979 (Item 4534)
      - AFT Higher Education Conference, AFT Commission on Higher Education, Sam Wakshull, Irwin Polishook, Apr 1, 1979 (Item 3415)
      - AFT National Advisory Committee on Higher Education, National Paraprofessional Committee, May 1, 1979 (Item 4185)
      - Feldman, Sandra, 1980 AFT Elections (Item 2939)
      - QuEST Conference, 1980 (Item 3960)
      - AFT Testing Conference [Includes but may not be limited to:] Hobart, Tom; LaValle, Kenneth (Senator); Pipho, Christopher, Feb 1980 (Item 3470)
      - AFT Lawyers Conference, May 1980 (Item 3415)
      - Paraprofessionals, AFT National Para Conf., May 1980 (Item 4979)
      - Scott, William T., QuEST Conference, May 1981 (Item 841)
      - Feldman, Sandra at AFT QuEST Conference, May 1981 (Item 852)
      - AFT Educational Research and Dissemination Program; Pilot Project in NYC under the Teachers Center Consortium, Sep 1981 (Item 5484)
      - Paraprofessionals, AFT National Para Conf., Oct 1981 (Item 4979)
      - AFT Educational Research and Dissemination Program Classroom Management Techniques Workshop, Dec 1981 (Item 5484)
      - QuEST, AFT Quest, 1985 (Item 3960)
      - Signing Ceremony, first collective bargaining contract, college administration and UFCT, undated (Item 339)
      - AFT Charter Presentation, undated (Item 480)
      - AFT Freedom Schools Program, undated (Item 480)
      - Education and Labor Meeting between AFT leaders and the House Committee on Education and Labor, undated (Item 1107)
      - AFT Legislative Support at Capitol Hill, Washington DC, undated (Item 1960)
      - AFT Legal Conference, undated (Item 3415)
      - AFT Leaders from Locals at intensive briefing on HEW labor appropriations bill, undated (Item 4619)
      - AFT Headquarters, undated (Item 5672)
  - Subseries I:D: Other Teacher Unions.
    - Sub-subseries I:D:1: Federation of Catholic Teachers
      - Federation of Catholic Teachers, Mar 1975 (Item 3662)
      - Catholic Teachers Federation [Federation of Catholic Teachers?], Jun 1975 (Item 3773)
      - Isenberg, Harold J. T. with Jack O'Neil after winning a new pact for Federation of Catholic Teachers, Nov 1975 (Item 3909)
      - Picketing by members of the Federation of Catholic Teachers paid off as the teachers forged a new contract with the Archdiocese of New York to avert a strike, Nov 16, 1975 (Item 3910)
      - Federation of Catholic Teachers, Harold Isenberg, J.P. Stevens Rally, Nov 1978 (Item 3662)
      - [Federation of?] Catholic Teachers with Cesar Chavez, 1979 (Item 3557)
      - Catholic Teachers, Lay Faculty Association with Federation of Catholic Teachers, Ficcio, Gordon, William Cea, 1979 (Item 3557)
      - [Federation of?] Catholic Teachers, Helen McDowell, Nov 1979 (Item 3557)
      - [Federation of?] Catholic Teachers, Picketing, Sep 1980 (Item 3557)
      - Catholic Teachers Association [Federation of Catholic Teachers?], Macchiarola, Fontana and Russo, Brooklyn, 1981 (Item 5397)
      - Federation of Catholic Teachers, undated (Item 3557)
      - [Federation of?] Catholic Teachers, JP Stevens Boycott, undated (Item 3557)
      - Catholic Teachers Federation [Includes but may not be limited to:] Sanders, Dan; Hobart, Tom; Shanker, Al, undated (Item 4141)
      - Labor Day Mass, Federation of Catholic Teachers, undated (Item 4582)
      - Federation of Catholic Teachers, undated (Item 5320)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:2: Lay Faculty Association
      - Brooklyn Catholic School Teacher Lay Faculty Association Picketing diocese, Sep 1972 (Item 2098)
      - Gordon, Robert M., Lay Faculty Association, Jul 1973 (Item 2212)
      - Lay Faculty Association, picketing AFT Department. of non-public schools, Sep 1973 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association Strike, Sep 1975 (Item 3862)
      - Christian Brothers Lay Faculty Association, May 1976 (Item 4390)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Mater Christi Strike, Sep 1979 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Workshop, Dec 1979 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Kenneth Hartnett, 1980 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Strike, Charles Sutera, 1981 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Reinstate Anne Moses, Arb. Win, May 1981 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Strike, General, Sep 1981 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Tom Hobart pledging support for, Oct 1981 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Strike, Oct 1981 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association, Christ the King HS, Local 3 Party for strikers, Dec 1981 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association picketing Christ the King HS, Farm Workers Support, etc., Jan 1982 (Item 1840)
      - Lay Faculty Association picketline, Apr 1982 (Item 1840)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:3: NEA
      - NEA Convention, Dallas, Texas, 1968 (Item 829)
      - NEA Board of Directors Meeting, May 1973 (Item 2512)
      - NEA Board, May 1973 (Item 2542)
      - NEA Convention, Jun 1973 (Item 1040)
      - NEA Leadership Training, Jun 1973 (Item 2602)
      - NEA Directors at NEA Convention, Jul 1973 (Item 1037)
      - Hobart, Tom receiving check from NEA ($1,020,000), Nov 1973 (Item 2791)
      - NEA Board Meeting, Nov 25, 1973 (Item 2512)
      - Harris, Jim (NEA President, Elect), Jul 1974 (Item 918)
      - NEA Convention, Jul 1974 (Item 1040)
      - NEA Board Meeting, Nov 1974 (Item 3478)
      - NEA Reception, Washington DC, Jan 1975 (Item 3536)
      - NEA Board Meeting, Tom Hobart, Feb 23, 1975 (Item 3461)
      - NEA Board of Director's Meeting, May 1975 (Item 3669)
      - [NEA] New York State Directors gather on White House Lawn, May 1975 (Item 3708)
      - NEA Leaders plant saplings in ITU's forest, in Judea, to symbolize ties between NEA and ITU, Jun 1975 (Item 3861)
      - NEA Convention, Jul 1975 (Item 1040)
      - NEA Board of Directors Meeting, Sep 1975 (Item 3669)
      - NEA Disaffiliation American Arbitration Association, Jan 1976 (Item 4008)
      - NEA Board Meeting, Feb 1976 (Item 4192)
      - Hobart, Tom (President), reviews NEA War on State, May 1976 (Item 4375)
      - Barrett, Catherine (NEA President) with Marjorie Carter (STA President), undated (Item 1090)
      - NEA Congressional Reception, undated (Item 3277)
      - Streif, Dean, NEA Board Meeting with Paul Cole, undated (Item 3478)
      - NEA Directors on White House Lawn, undated (Item 3780)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:4: New York State Federation of Teachers
      - NYS Federation [of Teachers] Convention, Nov 21, 1970 (Item 1210)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:5: NYEA
      - NYEA [New York Educator's Association, NEA], undated (Item 4316)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:6: SUFT
      - Swaim, Lucille with State University Federation of Teachers members, Jan 1971 (Item 1296)
      - Moynihan, Robert, Dr., Oneonta SUFT [State University Federation of Teachers] President and three scholarship winners, undated (Item 596)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:7: Teachers Guild
      - Teachers Guild, picketing City Hall, Charles Cogen, Al Smallheiser, Dave Wittes, Jack Schwartz, Jules Kolodny, undated (Item 5723)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:8: UTNY
      - UTNY Convention, 10/23-24/71, Oct 23, 1971 (Item 2598)
      - UTNY Presidents Weekend Conference, Arden House, 3/3-5/1972, Mar 3, 1972 (Item 1767)
      - UTNY Executive Council Meeting, Mar 10, 1972 (Item 1771)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:9: UUP
      - Delucia, Lawrence (President [UUP]), accepts congratulations after election, Jun 1973 (Item 2643)
      - Potsdam Local [of UUP?], School board and relations conf., Oct 1973 (Item 2355)
      - Potsdam Local [of UUP?], School board and relations conf. Grievance Workshop, Nov 1973 (Item 2355)
      - Schon, Tony congratulates Al DiRocco who by becoming a member of United University Profession, made his department 100% union, Feb 1975 (Item 3661)
      - Shanker, Al, UUP Delegate Assembly, Mar 1975 (Item 3597)
      - Hobart, Tom and Samuel Wakshull from United University Professions, May 1975 (Item 3848)
      - United University Professions Delegate Assembly, Feb 1976 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions Vote Count, Mar 1977 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions Vote count [Includes but may not be limited to:] Robisch, Ed; NYEA, Dec 1978 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions Delegate Assembly [Includes but may not be limited to:] Hobart, Tom; Behling, Ann Marie (Cobleskill); Sullivan, Ronald; Miller, Fred; Dolan, Peggy; Cimenelli, Diane; Quevedo, Lane, 1979 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions with SUNY Trustees, Feb 1979 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions, NYSUT Board, Mar 1979 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions, John Aiken, Mar 1979 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions, May 1979 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions, Potsdam UUP, Oct 1979 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions DA, Feb 1980 (Item 4512)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, Budget Cuts, Higher Ed Committee, PSC, Feb 1980 (Item 5236)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, May 1980 (Item 5236)
      - United University Professions with Rosalynn Carter, Oct 1980 (Item 4512)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, Oct 1980 (Item 5236)
      - United University Professions, SUNY Coalition, George Cooper to support higher education, Oct 1980 (Item 5321)
      - United University Professions Delegate Assembly [Includes but may not be limited to:] Geerkens, Mr., Mrs., and baby, 1981 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions at NYSUT Board of Directors Meeting, Jan 1981 (Item 4512)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, Feb 1981 (Item 5236)
      - United University Professions, Mar 1981 (Item 5321)
      - United University Professions PACE (Project For Adult College Education) [Includes but may not be limited to:] Brockport UUP, Apr 1981 (Item 5321)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, May 1981 (Item 5236)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, Sep 1981 (Item 5236)
      - United University Professions School of Optometry with legislators [Includes but may not be limited to:] Siegel, Mark; Pagano, Vincent, Oct 1981 (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions, Tom Hobart Meeting with Downstate Medical Center, Nov 1981 (Item 4512)
      - Livingston, Sam, profile, United University Professions, Feb 1982 (Item 4512)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly with Shanker, Feb 1982 (Item 5236)
      - Drescher, Nuala (UUP President), Profile, Mar 1982 (Item 5531)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, visiting professor from Poland, May 1982 (Item 5236)
      - Student Association of SUNY, United University Professions, undated (Item 3713)
      - United University Professions Downstate, undated (Item 4512)
      - UUP Delegates, NYSUT Representative Assembly, undated (Item 4512)
      - United University Professions - Drescher, Naula; Martin, Dennis; Ashe, Bernard; Rising, Gerald; Wakshull, Sam; Inventasch, Harvey; Skuse, Ray; Gheerkin, Henry; Hartman, Evelyn; Streif, Dean; Hicks, Cheryl; Sanders, Dan; Marchi, John; Cullinan, Marty; Alfrred SUNY; Stony Brook SUNY; Maritime SUNY; Forestry SUNY, undated (Item 4512CR)
      - Cobleskill College Chapter UUP September Meeting, undated (Item 4639)
      - UUP Delegate Assembly, Pace Buffalo State, undated (Item 5236)
    - Sub-subseries I:D:10: Miscellaneous
      - Washington [DC] Teachers Strike, Sep 22, 1972 (Item 2033)
      - Shanker, Al with Felix Rodriguez (President of Puerto Rico Federation of Teachers), Dec 1973 (Item 2806)
      - Puerto Rico Teachers Strike, Feb 1974 (Item 2893)
      - Timberlane Teachers [New Hampshire?] strike, Feb 1974 (Item 3117)
      - FEA [Florida Education Association] Representative Assembly, Apr 1974 (Item 2992)
      - Timberlane Teachers [New Hampshire?] Walkathon, Jun 1974 (Item 3117)
      - New Jersey College strike, Nov 1974 (Item 3454)
      - Latin American teacher unionists, South American Trade Unionists, May 1975 (Item 3670)
      - Beard, Priscilla from South Point Ohio Teachers Association, Sep 1975 (Item 3904)
      - United Professors of California Representation Campaign, May 1981 (Item 5445)
      - March, Sandra, Boston Teacher Union, three visitors, Nov 1981 (Item 3053)
      - Perth Amboy Strike, undated (Item 566)
  - Subseries I:E: Other Unions.
    - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers voting to Strike, Feb 1964 (Item 764)
    - Grape Pickers, Delano, California, Dec 1965 (Item 757)
    - Mexican-American Fam Workers Labor Confrontation with John Connally, Sep 1966 (Item 1676)
    - Apprentice bakers support UFT during mass resignations, 1967 (Item 313)
    - Grape Pickers Demonstration, UFT supports, Oct 1969 (Item 915)
    - Grape Workers Rally, Oct 10, 1969 (Item 1070)
    - Lil Roberts Jailing (DC 37), Nov 1969 (Item 1147)
    - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers Strike, 1970 (Item 1157)
    - Farm Workers prayer vigil, 1970 (Item 1305)
    - Abercrombie & Fitch Department Store Employees Strike, Jan 1971 (Item 1291)
    - Leukemia Strike by Teamster Locals and Management, San Diego, CA, Feb 1971 (Item 1483)
    - Military Support Mission Press Conference in support of United Farm Workers, San Diego, Calif., Mar 1971 (Item 1692)
    - PS 45 Queens, Visiting ILGWU, Apr 1971 (Item 1492)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers Demonstrate Against imports costing jobs in Boston, Apr 1971 (Item 1696)
    - District 25 painters picketline, Sep 1972 (Item 2153)
    - Trade Union representatives from Europe, Africa, Asia, and Latin America, visit UFT, Oct 1972 (Item 2014)
    - Actors Equity, Mar 1973 (Item 2273)
    - Oneita Knitting Mills, Andrews, South Carolina Strike, Mar 1973 (Item 2334)
    - Women's Rights Conference, Philadelphia, PA [Philadelphia Federation of Teachers and Pennsylvania Federation of Teachers], May 1973 (Item 2513)
    - New Film, "The People Against Willie Farah", Nov 1973 (Item 2767)
    - Shanker, Al meeting with Japanese union leaders, Dec 1973 (Item 2810)
    - Custodial Workers Strike, Jan 1974 (Item 2799)
    - Farah Solidarity Depot, Apr 1974 (Item 3026)
    - Public Employees Federation Founding Convention, Nov 1974 (Item 3467)
    - Shanker, Al meets with German unionists representing metal workers, mine workers, chemical workers, and public service communications workers, Nov 1974 (Item 3475)
    - Picketing, Trade Unionists picket department store as part of protest by clothing workers against importation of apparel from countries which pay low wages, Nov 1974 (Item 3481)
    - Webber, Clyde at Labor News Conference with President of Firefighters William McClennan, 1975 (Item 3518)
    - Pidgeon, Walter Receiving award from Screen Actors Guild, presented by Dennis Weaver, Feb 1975 (Item 3514)
    - Teacher Locals rally in Central Labor Council in support of Telephone workers (Rochester, NY), Mar 1975 (Item 3650)
    - Abel, I.W., President United Steelworkers of America, with NYSUT Officers, Mar 1975 (Item 3655)
    - Rochester Telephone Co. ends Strike, Jun 1975 (Item 3704)
    - Garment Industry, union leaders are honored, Jun 1975 (Item 3723)
    - ILGWU, Jun 1975 (Item 3819)
    - Transit Workers Demonstration, Aug 1975 (Item 3823)
    - Brotherhood of Sleeping Car Porters, 50th Anniversary Dinner, Oct 1975 (Item 3921)
    - United Farm Workers President Cesar Chavez meets with AFL-CIO special subcommittee, Nov 1975 (Item 3891)
    - Altomare, George with Nick Jones, NYC Rep. for United Farm Workers, is presented with check, Nov 1975 (Item 3935)
    - Screen Actors Guild, SAG Award, Jan 1976 (Item 3991)
    - Academy Awards, Oscars will continue to bear the union label [Jewelry Workers Local 23], Mar 1976 (Item 4129)
    - ILGWU Local 23-25, Chinese American Voters League encourage voter registration, Apr 1976 (Item 4298)
    - Whitesboro, School Staffers CSEA For NYSUT, Apr 1976 (Item 4305)
    - Labor Urges Full Funding for the Arts [Includes but may not be limited to:] Hyman, Earl, Actor's Equity, May 1976 (Item 4244)
    - Melanie [Safka], Benefit Concert for the United Farm Workers, May 1976 (Item 4258)
    - Firestone Products, Rubber Workers picketing of Firestone outlets and retail stores, May 1976 (Item 4275)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers Demonstration, Dec 1976 (Item 1696)
    - Whitesboro Employees Union, Feb 1977 (Item 4305)
    - Lakeland Federation of Teachers, Joseph Barni Thanks Steelworkers, Apr 1978 (Item 4809)
    - Hopkins, Ned testifying against PEF, May 1978 (Item 2059)
    - PEF Victory, World Trade Center Press Conference (Hobart, DiLeonardis, Sander, etc.), Jul 20, 1978 (Item 4865)
    - Labor, Wilkes Barre Federal Workers Protest, 1979 (Item 4244)
    - PEF Convention, 1979 (Item 4879)
    - Postal Workers, UFT Supports, Feb 1979 (Item 5108)
    - UFT Supports Postal Workers Strike, Mar 1979 (Item 1319)
    - Strike, School Bus Drivers Strike, Mar 1979 (Item 3896)
    - United Farm Workers, UFT Demonstration, Apr 1979 (Item 3891)
    - Price Watch ILGWU, Jun 1979 (Item 1623)
    - Japanese Delegates, Japanese Educators, Jun 1979 (Item 4841)
    - United Nations International School / Staff Association Negotiating Committee, Jun 1979 (Item 5193)
    - UFT Supports Department Store Workers, A & S Rally, Sep 1979 (Item 1319)
    - United Farm Workers, City Council supports boycott, Oct 1979 (Item 3891)
    - AFTRA Strike, Summer 1980 and Screen Actor Guild (Item 734)
    - Transport Workers Union, President John Lawe, Richard Ravitch, Transit Strike 1980 (Item 3823)
    - Screen Actors Guild, Summer 1980 [x] (Item 3991)
    - J.P. Stevens, Michael Mann and George Altomare at Sperry, Anti-J.P. Stevens, 1980 (Item 4489)
    - NY Historical Society Strike, Spring 1980 [District 65 UAW] (Item 5266)
    - Casey, Terry (Gen. Secretary) National Association of Schoolmasters Union of Women Teachers of Great Britian at 1980 AFT Convention (Item 5282)
    - Labor, Iron Workers protest American hostage in Iran situation, Jan 1980 (Item 4244)
    - Transit Workers Demonstration, Rally, City Hall, Mar 1980 (Item 3823)
    - PEF Legislative Reception, Mar 4, 1980 (Item 4879)
    - Koch, Ed, Mayor, Transit Strike, Apr 1980 (Item 1986)
    - Transit Workers, UFT Supports Transport Workers Strike, Apr 1980 (Item 3823)
    - PEF Intro to Legislators, Apr 1980 (Item 4879)
    - United Farm Workers Lettuce Boycott, "Red Coach", May 1980 (Item 3891)
    - ILGWU with President James Earl Carter at factory, Oct 1980 (Item 3819)
    - J.P. Stevens, Workers Cheer first CBA, Oct 1980 (Item 4489)
    - PEF Convention, Oct 1980 (Item 4879)
    - PEF Exec. Board, Nov 1980 (Item 4879)
    - Federation of Professional Athletes, President Ed Garvey at news conference, Nov 1980 (Item 5324)
    - PEF Check to NAACP, Dec 1980 (Item 4879)
    - Texas International Airlines, Picketing creation of New York Air, Runaway shop, Dec 1980 (Item 5372)
    - PS 54 Staten Island, TWU [Transport Workers Union] Fund, Mar 1981 (Item 3703)
    - ILGWU President Sol Chaiken testifies at House Hearing on "homework", Apr 1981 (Item 3819)
    - Labor News Conference, Richard W. Cortdz, Secretary Treasurer Of Service Employees [International Union], May 1981 (Item 2076)
    - PEF, Two Agreements, May 1981 (Item 4879)
    - PEF Retiree Group Lobbying, Jun 1981 (Item 4879)
    - Benjamin Rush Employees United, Beth Fitzpatrick BREU Organizing Committee, Jun 1981 (Item 5427)
    - AFL-CIO Executive Council member, Douglas A. Fraser, Auto Workers, Sep 1981 (Item 3671)
    - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers, Striking, 2000 arrested, Sep 20, 1981 (Item 1157)
    - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers Supporters of strikers at City Hall Rally, Sep 27, 1981 (Item 1157)
    - Philadelphia Federation of Teachers Strike Rally, Oct 1981 (Item 1157)
    - PEF (Public Employees Fund) NYS Political Action Convention with Hobart, Oct 1981 (Item 4879)
    - PEF Union Label, Oct 1981 (Item 4879)
    - PEF Convention, Oct 1981 (Item 4879)
    - Asner, Edward, Elected President, Screen Actors Guild, Oct 1981 (Item 5494)
    - United Farm Workers, Cesar Chavez Press Conference with Students, Nov 1981 (Item 3891)
    - Public Employees Federation, Bargaining, Kraemer and Connie Cabell, Nov 1981 (Item 4879)
    - Public Employees Federation, 1/2 hour program, "Contract Countdown": Shown on TV, 11/81, Nov 1981 (Item 4879)
    - PEF Press Conference, Progress on Day Care Centers, Kraemer, Dec 7, 1981 (Item 4879)
    - North Syracuse Education Association collection for Christmas presents for striking PATCO members, Jan 1982 (Item 4665)
    - PEF Demonstration at Reg. Dept. of Labor, Feb 1982 (Item 4879)
    - PEF Contract Signing, Feb 1982 (Item 4879)
    - United Farm Workers, Manhattan Demonstration supporting Andy Boy broccoli and Double-O lettuce boycott, Feb 14, 1982 (Item 3891)
    - AFTRA Strike, urge public support for Equal Rights Amendment at press conference, NYC, Mar 1982 (Item 734)
    - PEF, Kraemer and Conti Meeting, Mar 1982 (Item 4879)
    - PEF First Pre-Retirement program given, Mar 1982 (Item 4879)
    - Italian-American Studies, Visit by Italian Trade Unionists, Apr 1982 (Item 4407)
    - PEF Benefit Fund Meeting, Apr 1982 (Item 4879)
    - AFTRA Strike settled, filing of charges against Westinghouse, May 1982 (Item 734)
    - Feldman, Sandra with Ted Elsberg of CSA [Council of School Supervisors and Administrators] at Emergency Budget Meeting, May 1982 (Item 852)
    - Hoke, Elizabeth (PEF President), rally, 1983 (Item 5585)
    - Greyhound Strike Rally, Nov 1983 (Item 5607)
    - Guinan, Matthew, International President, Transport Workers Union of America, AFL-CIO, undated (Item 123)
    - Shanker, Al with [United Electrical, Radio, and Machine Workers of America President] Paul Jennings (UFT contribution of $40,000), undated (Item 161)
    - AFTRA Picketline, undated (Item 188)
    - Chemists Strike [Local 1199], undated (Item 446)
    - Hotel, Motel and Club Employees Union, Local 6, Strike, undated (Item 448)
    - Taxicab Drivers Strike, undated (Item 449)